[
  {
    "name": "Слова",
    "cards": [
      {
        "question": "Привет",
        "answer": "Hello"
      },
      {
        "question": "Мир",
        "answer": "World"
      },
      {
        "question": "Вода",
        "answer": "Water"
      },
      {
        "question": "Огонь",
        "answer": "Fire"
      },
      {
        "question": "Земля",
        "answer": "Earth"
      },
      {
        "question": "Воздух",
        "answer": "Air"
      },
      {
        "question": "Дом",
        "answer": "House"
      },
      {
        "question": "Семья",
        "answer": "Family"
      },
      {
        "question": "Друг",
        "answer": "Friend"
      },
      {
        "question": "Время",
        "answer": "Time"
      },
      {
        "question": "Любовь",
        "answer": "Love"
      },
      {
        "question": "Работа",
        "answer": "Work"
      },
      {
        "question": "Еда",
        "answer": "Food"
      },
      {
        "question": "Деньги",
        "answer": "Money"
      },
      {
        "question": "Город",
        "answer": "City"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "Вопросительные слова",
    "cards": [
      {
        "question": "Почему?",
        "answer": "Why?"
      },
      {
        "question": "Что?",
        "answer": "What?"
      },
      {
        "question": "Когда?",
        "answer": "When?"
      },
      {
        "question": "Где?",
        "answer": "Where?"
      },
      {
        "question": "Кто?",
        "answer": "Who?"
      },
      {
        "question": "Как?",
        "answer": "How?"
      },
      {
        "question": "Который?",
        "answer": "Which?"
      },
      {
        "question": "Чей?",
        "answer": "Whose?"
      },
      {
        "question": "Сколько? (неисчисляемое)",
        "answer": "How much?"
      },
      {
        "question": "Сколько? (исчисляемое)",
        "answer": "How many?"
      },
      {
        "question": "Как часто?",
        "answer": "How often?"
      },
      {
        "question": "Как долго?",
        "answer": "How long?"
      },
      {
        "question": "Как далеко?",
        "answer": "How far?"
      },
      {
        "question": "Во сколько?",
        "answer": "What time?"
      },
      {
        "question": "Какой тип?",
        "answer": "What kind of?"
      }
    ]
  }
]
